<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Export generator="Cache" version="25">
<Class name="TK.Zen.component.rivVersion">
<Description>
TK.Zen.component.rivVersion</Description>
<Super>%ZEN.Component.dataCombo</Super>
<TimeCreated>62879,21177.078077</TimeCreated>

<Parameter name="NAMESPACE">
<Description>
This is the XML namespace for this component.</Description>
<Default>http://www.intersystems.com/zen/custom</Default>
</Parameter>

<Parameter name="XMLNAME">
<Default>rivVersion</Default>
</Parameter>

<Property name="columnHeaders">
<Description>
If defined, this is a comma-delimited list of column
headers displayed in the dropdown list.</Description>
<Type>%ZEN.Datatype.csv</Type>
<InitialExpression>"Name"</InitialExpression>
<Parameter name="ZENLOCALIZE" value="1"/>
</Property>

<Property name="displayColumns">
<Description>
If there are multiple data columns displayed in the dropdown list,
this optional property defines a comma-delimited list of the column numbers
of the column that should be displayed.</Description>
<Type>%ZEN.Datatype.csv</Type>
<InitialExpression>"2"</InitialExpression>
<Parameter name="ZENSETTING" value="0"/>
</Property>

<Property name="choiceColumn">
<Description><![CDATA[
If there are multiple data columns displayed within the dropdown list
this is the column number (1-based) of the column that will provide the display
value for this control.<br>
If this value is greater than the number of columns in the query
then the second column will be used.]]></Description>
<Type>%ZEN.Datatype.integer</Type>
<InitialExpression>2</InitialExpression>
<Parameter name="MINVAL" value="1"/>
<Parameter name="ZENSETTING" value="0"/>
</Property>

<Property name="sql">
<Description><![CDATA[
(optional) SQL statement that, if present, will be used to 
create a <class>%ResultSet</class> object.<br>
If defined, this takes precedence over 
<property>queryClass</property> and <property>queryName</property>.]]></Description>
<Type>%ZEN.Datatype.sql</Type>
<InitialExpression>"SELECT Id, Namn FROM TK.Rivversion"</InitialExpression>
</Property>

<Property name="sqlLookup">
<Description><![CDATA[
(optional) SQL statement that, given a value, finds a display
value to show in the combo box. If present, this is used
to find a display value for a given logical value.<br>
The value of this property should be an SQL statement that
returns a single row containing a display value for a given logical value.
When this query is executed, a logical value is provided as a query
input parameter (i.e., as a ? within the SQL statement.<br>
For example:<br>
<example language="html">
sqlLookup="SELECT Name FROM MyApp.MyTable WHERE ID = ?" 
</example>]]></Description>
<Type>%ZEN.Datatype.sql</Type>
<InitialExpression>"SELECT Namn FROM TK.Rivversion WHERE Id = ?"</InitialExpression>
<Parameter name="ZENSETTING" value="0"/>
</Property>

<Property name="cached">
<Description><![CDATA[
If true (the default is false) then the following behavior occurs:
<ol>
<li>When the page is first displayed, a query is executed to fetch the initial contents of the dropdown. The <property>itemCount</property> property
will be set to the number of items within the dropdown.</li>
<li>The client will use these results instead of going back to the server to fetch the contents of the dropdown.</li>
</ol>
The <method>clearCache</method will clear the dropdown cache, so will
modifying the search parameters for the query.]]></Description>
<Type>%ZEN.Datatype.boolean</Type>
<InitialExpression>1</InitialExpression>
</Property>

<Property name="editable">
<Description>
If true, then this is an editable combobox (a user can directly edit the value within the input box).</Description>
<Type>%ZEN.Datatype.boolean</Type>
<InitialExpression>1</InitialExpression>
</Property>

<Property name="searchKeyLen">
<Description><![CDATA[
If non-zero, this is the maximum number of search characters
taken from the combo input box and passed as a parameter to 
the query (defined by <property>sql</property> that provides the contents of the dropdown box.<br>
If zero, then the contents of the input box are not used as a parameter.]]></Description>
<Type>%ZEN.Datatype.integer</Type>
<InitialExpression>2</InitialExpression>
<Parameter name="MINVAL" value="0"/>
</Property>

<Property name="maxRows">
<Description><![CDATA[
Maximum number of rows to fetch from the <class>%ResultSet</class> object.
This provides a way to limit the number of rows displayed by a data-aware component.<br/>
If this is set to 0, then no limit is enforced; all rows from the query are displayed.]]></Description>
<Type>%ZEN.Datatype.integer</Type>
<InitialExpression>0</InitialExpression>
</Property>
</Class>
</Export>
